좋아, 아무 카드나
하나 골라
Okay, pick a card.
Any card.
잘 외워둬
All right, now memorize it.
다른 애들한테도 보여줘
Show it to everybody.
봤어?
Got it?
좋아, 나한테 줘
All right.
Give it back to me.
하트 5
Five of hearts.
Real magic does exist.
- 진짜 대단한데
- 와우!
- 조이, 어떻게 한 거야?
- 말해주면 안되지
Joey, how do you do it?
I can't tell you that.
윗집에 누가 왔나 보네
Somebody's at the door on the ceiling.
위층에 사는 사람
너무 시끄러워
That's our unbelievably loud
upstairs neighbor.
He took up the carpets,
and now you can hear everything.
카펫을 치우니까
여기서도 다 들리는 거야
올라가서 조용히 좀
걸어다니라고 하면 안돼?
Why don't you go ask him
to just, "Step lightly, please?"
몇 번이나 얘기했지
I have, like five times.
But the guy is so charming...
근데 너무나 매력적인 사람이라
화내러 갔다가 사과만 하고 와
... I go up there to yell,
then I end up apologizing to him.
그런 게 어딨어?
That is silly!
내가 올라가서 조용히 하라고
얘기할게
I'll go up and tell him
to keep it down.
- 좋을 대로 해
- 행운을 빈다
-All right, be my guest.
-Good luck.
좋아, 좋아...
All right, all right...
...if you wanna know how I did it,
I'll show you.
어떻게 했는지 알고 싶으면
알려줄게
너희가 카드를 줄 때
When you handed me back the card,
what you didn't see was...
엄청 빠른 속도로 슬쩍 보는 거야
육안으로 확인이 안 될 만큼
... I looked at it so fast,
it was invisible to the naked eye.
방금 봤어
I just did it.
Just did it again.
또 봤어
너희도 볼 수 있게
천천히 할게
Here, I'll slow it down
so you guys can see it. Ready?
- 그랬구나
- 그래
-I got it now!
-Okay.
Thank you.
고마워요
The One Where Chandler
Can't Remember Which Sister
안녕
내 키만큼 되고 끝이 올가미처럼
생긴 밧줄 없니?
Anybody got a length of rope about
6 feet long, with a noose at the end?
- 무슨 일 있었어?
- 재니스를 봤어
-Honey, what's the matter?
-I just saw Janice.
남편이랑 스케이트를 타는데
너무나 행복해 보였어
She was at Rockefeller Center, skating
with her husband. She looked so happy.
기분이 나빠서 애들 먹는
과자를 뺏어서 집어던졌지
I almost feel bad for whipping
that kid's pretzel at them.
나도 캐더린이랑 헤어지고
처음 봤던 생각이 난다
I remember the first time I saw
Katherine after we broke up.
도나란 친구하고
웃으면서 걸어가는데
She was walking and talking
with her friend, Donna.
God, it killed me!
죽겠더라구
그날 셋이 만나서
침대에서 뒹굴었다며?
But you ended up having sex
with both of them that afternoon.
Sorry, I just
Any excuse to tell that story.
미안, 그 일에 대해선 뭐라고
할 말이 없다
챈들러, 내일 파티에 오면
기분이 나아질 거야
There's a party tomorrow.
You'll feel better then.
난 괜찮아, 날 위해서
파티까지 열 필요는 없어
I'm gonna be okay. You don't
have to throw a party for me.
조이 생일이야
It's Joey's birthday.
Then if anybody should have a party,
it should be him.
파티라면 조이 같은
친구를 위해 열어야지
아직도 저기 있어?
I cannot believe
she's still up there.
농담을 저렇게 하면 안되지
Well, he totally
screwed up the punch line.
이렇게 말했어야지
You know, it's supposed to be
커피 어떻게 됐어요?
How's that coffee coming, dear?
지금 드릴게요
Right away, Mr. IKaplan.
I'm not suppose to drink it.
It makes me gassy.
커피 마시면 안되는데...
자꾸 가스가 나와서...
알아요
I know.
패션 일을 하려고 들어왔는데
웬 커피 심부름이냐 생각하죠?
I'll bet you're thinking,
"What's an intelligent girl...
...who wants to be in fashion
doing making coffee?"
잘 아시네요
You got me.
가능성을 보지 않는다고는
생각하지 말아요
Don't think I haven't noticed
your potential.
패션에 관계되는 프로젝트를
맡길까 하는데, 어때요?
I've got a project for you
that's a lot more related to fashion.
-How does that sound?
-That sounds great!
좋죠
- 이리 와요
- 정말 감사합니다
-Come on over here, sweetheart.
-Thank you so much.
- 이리
- 고마워요
이 행거들을 빠른 시간 내에
분리해줘요
I need these hangers separated
ASAP.
수고해요
You're welcome.
내 일이 싫어, 너무나 싫어
내 일이 너무 싫어
Oh, God, I hate my job!
I hate it.
I know, honey. I'm sorry.
정말 안됐다
때려치고 싶기도 하고
계속 다니고 싶기도 한데...
I want to quit, but then I think l
should stick it out.
이렇게 힘든 직장에 왜
꼭 붙어 있어야 하는 거야?
Then I think:
"Why would a person stay
in such a demeaning job...
아주 희미하게라도 내가
관심을 갖고 있는 분야니까?
...just because it's remotely related
to the field they're interested in?
낸들 알겠니
Gee, I don't know, Rach.
주문하세요, 옌틀 수프, 제임스
빈스, 하우디, 두디도 있어요
Order up! Yentl soup, James Beans,
and a Howdy, hold the Doody.
미안해, 난...
일이 힘들어서가 아냐
Come on, I'm sorry.
I didn't
I don't mind paying my dues.
온종일 화장실만 들락거리는데
패션 일을 어떻게 배우겠어?
But how much
will I learn about fashion...
... by walking Myra,
the arthritic seamstress...
...to the bathroom?
Hi.
이봐요, 제 고통이
댁의 기쁨인가요?
Is my misery amusing to you?
죄송합니다, 전 그냥...
I'm sorry, I was just....
웃지 말아요
이건 내 일이라구요
It's not funny.
This is actually my job.
Believe me, I've been there.
옛날 생각이 나서요
전 마네킨 머리를
분류하는 일을 했죠
I had to sort mannequin heads
at that Mannequins Plus.
그럼 전 친구랑 하던 얘길
계속 해야겠으니까
I'm just gonna go back
to talking to my friend here.
댁은 햄버거나 마저 드시죠
You can go back to enjoying
your little hamburger.
- 한 마디만 할까요?
- 뭔데요?
Just one other thing.
전 블루밍데일에 다니는데
일자리를 알아봐 드릴까요?
I work at Bloomingdale's.
I might know of a possible job,
if you're interested.
피클 드실래요?
Do you want my pickle?
Hey, guys.
안녕하세요
-Hey, Gunther.
-Hi.
- 안녕, 건터
- 안녕
위층에 사는 시끄러운 남자랑
데이트할 거라구?
You're going on a date
with the noisy guy upstairs?
정말 멋진 남자야
Well, he's very charming.
너무 멋져 탈이지, 너랑 사귀면
그 남자를 미워할 수가 없잖아
He's too charming!
But if you go out,
it'll be harder for me to hate him.
그래도 노력은 해봐
You'll just have to try.
조이, 젤로 어딨어?
Joey? Where are the Jell-O shots?
몰라, 챈들러가 가져갔는데...
I don't know. Chandler's
supposed to be passing them
챈들러?
Chandler!
안뇽
Hello-dee-lo!
방방 떴군
Well, somebody's feeling better.
-Stick out your tongue!
-Take off your shirt!
- 혀 내밀어봐
- 옷 벗어봐
-Oh, my!
-Oh, my God!
- 맙소사
- 세상에
몇 개나 먹은 거야?
이건 거의 보드카 수준인데
How many did you have?
They're pure vodka.
엄마가 만들어준
젤로 맛이야
Yeah, Jell-O.
Just like Mom used to make.
The most unbelievable thing
happened today.
오늘 정말 기적 같은
일이 있었어
- 안녕
모니카 가게에서 점심 먹는데
블루밍데일에 다니는 남자가
I had lunch at Monica's
and met a guy...
...who works for a buyer
at Bloomingdale's.
자기네 부서에서 사람을
뽑는다잖아
There's an opening there!
So I gave him my phone number...
그래서 전화번호를 줬더니
주말까지 전화해주겠대
...and he'll call me this weekend
to get me an interview!
- 그래?
- 정말이야
아무 이유 없이 자기를
도와준다는 거야?
So this guy's helping you
for no apparent reason?
처음 보는 사람인데?
And he's a total stranger?
응, '마크 뭐'라는 사람이야
Yeah. His name is "Mark" something.
'마크 뭐'라는 사람이
섹스가 고픈 모양이네
Sounds like "Mark Something"
wants to have some sex!
뭐?
What?
그러니까...
처음 보는 사람이 아무 이유
없이 자길 왜 돕는데?
Why else would he swoop
in out of nowhere for no reason?
친절한 사람이니까?
To be nice?
Hey, Joey, are men ever nice
to strange women for no reason?
조이, 남자가 모르는 여자한테
이유도 없이 친절을 베풀까?
- 섹스가 급한 거야
- 고맙다
-No, only for sex.
-Thank you.
'마크 뭐'라는 사람한테
내 얘기도 했어?
So did you tell
"Mark Something" about me?
그럴 필요 없었어
I didn't have to.
I was wearing...
'로스를 사랑해' 광고판을
항상 갖고 다니거든
... my "I Heart Ross" sandwich board
and ringing my bell.
- 조이 오빠, 생일 축하해
- 어서들 와
Joey!
Happy birthday!
양다리를 몇 개나
걸치는 거야?
How many of that girl are you seeing?
무슨 소리야?
다 조이 동생들이잖아
How hammered are you?
These are Joey's sisters.
Hi, Joey's sisters!
- 안녕, 조이 동생들!
- 안녕
뭐 마시는 거예요?
What're we drinking over here?
보드카랑 크랜베리 주스요
Well, I have a vodka
and cranberry juice.
No kidding?
설마, 남편 쏴죽이고 만들어
마신 거랑 똑같네
That's the same drink I made myself
right after I shot my husband.
뭐라고 할 말이 없네요
Okay, I don't know how
to talk to you.
뭐해요?
What are you doing?
옛날 여자친구 단축키
없애는 중이에요
I'm taking my ex-girlfriend
off my speed dialer.
아뇨, 좋은 거예요
No, it's a good thing.
전화 빨리 걸어서 뭐해요?
급하게 갈 필요 없잖아요?
Why must we dial so speedily anyway?
Why rush through life?
Why can't we savor
the precious moments?
소중한 순간들을 간직해야죠
가슴 한번 대빵 크다
You have some huge breasts!
- 안녕
-Hi.
레이첼이 '마크 뭐'라는 남자를
만났다면서?
So I heard about this Mark guy
that Rachel met today.
Isn't it great?
- 굉장하지 않아?
- 그래
Yeah, pretty good.
He sounds like a nice, good guy.
그래, 굉장하지
정말 좋은 사람 같더라
Oh, he is.
And he is so dreamy!
환상이야, 그거 알아?
I mean, when he left,
I actually used the phrase:
그 사람 간 뒤에 나도 모르게
'어머나, 어머나' 했다니까
"Hummina, hummina, hummina."
미치겠군
That's excellent.
좋은 사람이라고?
So he's "just a nice guy."
Do you really think this Mark
doesn't want anything for helping you?
마크가 정말 아무 대가 없이
자길 도와준다고 생각해?
샤워라도 같이 해줄까봐
Well, I assume I'll
have to take showers with him.
그게 인간으로서 기본 예의지
But that's true of any job.
How you feeling?
좀 어때?
Well, my apartment isn't
there anymore...
우리집이 없어져버렸어
내가 다 마셔 없애 버렸거든
... because I drank it.
어디로 없어진 거야?
선물 다 뜯어놓고 없어졌던데
Where'd you go? We lost you
after you opened up all the presents.
창고에 누워 있더라구
그것도 혼자가 아니었어
I ended up in the storage room,
and not alone.
- 우후!
- '우후'가 아냐, '우후'가 아냐
No "woo-hooing." No "woo-hooing."
왜, 무슨 일 있었어?
Why, what happened?
조이 동생이랑 일 저질렀어
I fooled around with Joey's sister.
근데 그게 다가 아냐
That's not the worst part.
또 뭐가 있는데?
What is the worst part?
어느 동생인지를 모르겠어
I can't remember which sister.
You see what men do?
Don't tell me men are nice.
봐, 남자들이 친절하다고?
이런 게 남자야!
This is men!
미쳤어?
Are you insane?
조이가 널 죽이려고 할 거야
정말 죽일 거라구
Joey will kill you.
He'll actually kill you dead.
You don't think I thought of that?
나라고 그런 생각
안한 줄 알아?
어떻게 누군지
모를 수가 있어?
-How can you not know which one?
-That's unbelievable.
정말 기가 막히다
- 혹시 지나 아냐?
- 지나가 누구야?
-Was it Gina?
-Which one's Gina?
검은 머리에 왕방울 만한
귀걸이한 여자
The dark, big hair,
with airplane earrings.
그건 지나가 아니라
디나야
That's Dina, not Gina.
See? You can't tell
which is which either!
봐, 너희도 누가 누군지
모르잖아, 이얍!
우린 걔들이랑 일 저지르진
않았어, 이얍, 이얍!
We didn't fool around
with any of them.
It's got to be Veronica.
The girl in the red skirt.
아마 베로니카일 거야
빨간 스커트 입은 여자
그 여자 목에 내 혀가
달라붙었었거든
I definitely stuck my tongue
down her throat!
That was me.
그건 나였어
내가 술을 마시면 가끔
너무 친하게 구는 경향이 있어
When I drink, sometimes
I get overly friendly...
- 미안해
- 괜찮아
-...and I'm sorry.
-That's okay.
- 그래
- 괜찮겠지
-That's all right.
-That's okay.
잠깐 나 좀 볼래?
Can I talk to you for a second?
- 안녕, 조이
- 안녕
Hey, Joey!
Come on.
나와
Why can't we talk in here...
여기서 하면 안돼?
증인들 앞에서
...with witnesses?
I just got off the phone
with my sister.
방금 내 동생이랑 통화했어
누구?
Which one?
메리 안젤라
-Mary Angela.
- 메리 안젤라...
- 그래
Now which one is she again?
그게 누군데?
챈들러한테 물어보지 그래?
걔랑 사고친 건 챈들러니까
Ask Chandler.
He fooled around with her.
She told me you said
you could really fall for her.
정말 그 애한테 빠진 거야?
Is that true, or are you just getting
over Janice by groping my sister?
아니면, 재니스를 잊으려고
내 동생을 이용한 거야?
아마 첫 번째일걸
It's gotta be the first one.
정말? 잘됐다
Really?
That's great!
You and my sister, sitting in a tree!
너랑 내 동생이
한 배를 타다니
그래, 한 배를 탔지
Yep, I'm in a tree.
전화왔어?
마크가 전화했어?
Did he call? Did Mark call?
아니, 미안
아직 주말은 안 끝났어
I'm sorry.
But the weekend's not over yet.
세상에, 피비야?
Oh, my God! Is that Phoebe?
데이트하고 돌아왔나봐
Guess they're back from their date.
Music!
음악까지, 죽이는데
Very nice!
맙소사
Oh, my God!
So how are you?
그래, 넌 어때?
좋아, 책 다 읽었어
-I am good. I finished my book.
-What's it about?
그래? 무슨 내용인데?
몰라, 우리 나갈래?
I don't remember.
Do you want to take a walk?
그러자
메리 안젤라에게
"Dear Mary Angela:
안녕, 잘 지내?
Hi, how's it going?
내 평생 이렇게 쓰기 힘든
편지는 처음이야
This is the hardest letter
I've ever had to write."
너 미쳤어?
What the hell's the matter with you?
편지로 끝내려는 거 알면
조이가 가만 있겠어?
How will Joey react to you
blowing off his sister with a letter?
그러니까 나 프랑스
갔다고 얘기해달라니까
That's where you tell him
that I moved to France...
그러고 난 쿠바로 뜨려고
...when actually I'll be in Cuba.
이건 직접 가서
해결해야 할 일이야
Look, you've got to do this
yourself in person.
이름은 알았잖아
You know her name.
집에 찾아가서 메리 안젤라를
만나는 거야
You just go to the house
and ask for Mary Angela.
누구든 문을 열고 나오면
데리고 나가서 진정을 시키라구
When whichever one she is
comes to the door...
...take her for a walk
and let her down easy.
메리 안젤라가 나왔는데
메리 안젤라를 불러달라고 하면?
What if she comes to the door
and I ask for her?
Where in Cuba?
쿠바 어디?
조이...
너 여기서 뭐해?
What are you doing here?
할머니가 빨래하러 가셔서
기다리는 중이야, 넌?
Waiting for my grandma
to do my laundry.
What about you?
메리 안젤라 보러 왔지
I'm here to see Mary Angela.
넌 멋진 놈이야
들어와
You are so the man! Come on.
참, 있잖아
Now look, listen.
Listen....
할머니는 둘 사이 아직
모르시니까 너무 티내지 마
Be cool, because Grandma
doesn't know about you two.
You don't want to tick her off.
무솔리니 시체에 여섯 번째로
침뱉은 분이니까 조심해야 돼
She was, like, the sixth person
to spit on Mussolini's hanging body.
Where's Mary Angela?
메리 안젤라 어딨어?
- 안에 있지
- 좋아
She's right in there.
안녕, 챈들러
-Hey, Chandler!
마크가 왜 전화를 안 하지?
벌써 토요일 밤인데
I can't believe Mark didn't call.
It's Sunday night and he didn't call.
그럴줄 알았지
Bummer.
그래, 고소해 죽겠지?
Yeah, right. Look at you.
You're practically giddy.
천만에, 마크 일이 안돼서
진짜 유감이야
I'm genuinely sorry
the Mark thing didn't work out.
레이첼, 난 자기가 잘 되기만
바라고 있어
Look, Rach, I want
only good things for you.
Wait a minute.
Why don't you just call Mark?
잠깐, 네가 전화하지 그래?
Who says you have to sit
and wait for him?
가만 앉아서 기다릴 거 있어?
직접 나서보는 거야
You've got to make stuff happen!
Yeah, but you don't
wanna seem too pushy.
그럼 너무 속보이지 않을까?
속이 보이다니
마크가 집 전화번호를 줬는걸
It's not pushy.
He gave her his home number.
집 전화번호를 줬어?
집 번호를?
He gave you his home number,
as in, to his home?
그래, 내가 잘되길 바란다면
전화해도 괜찮겠지?
And you don't mind if I call,
because you want good things for me.
That's right, good things.
That is what I said.
그럼, 잘 돼야지
내 말이 그 말이야
여보세요, 마크?
안녕, 레이첼 그린이에요
Mark? Hi, it's Rachel Greene.
Oh, no.
Don't you apologize.
아뇨, 미안할 거 없어요
기다릴게요
Yeah, I'll hold.
He left my number at work.
내 번호를 회사에 두고 왔는데
조카 리포트 도와주는 중이었대
Then he had to help his niece
with her report on the pioneers.
That is so made up!
뻔한 수작이야
세상에, 내일요?
아뇨, 전 좋아요
Oh, my God! Tomorrow?
That's
No, it's perfect.
Oh, God!
Thank you so much!
정말 고마워요
네, 안녕
Great.
I got the interview!
- 내일 면접 보러 오래
- 잘됐다
정말!
There you go!
내일 점심 때 만나서
준비하는 거 도와주겠대
He even offered to meet me for lunch
and prep me for it.
정말 잘됐다
That is amazing!
내가 마크라면...
마크를 좀 알 것 같은데...
Well, if I know Mark,
and I think I do...
기대 않는 게 좋을걸
...I'd expect nothing less.
뭘 입고 가지?
I gotta figure out what to wear.
High collar and baggy pants say,
"I'm a pro!"
뻣뻣한 칼라에 헐렁한 바지
프로답게 보여야지
좋아, 그럼 나중에 보자
Yeah, right.
Okay, I'll see you guys later.
잘 해봐
You go get them!
내가 너한테 뭘 잘못했어?
뭘 잘못했는데 이래?
What did I do to you?
Did I hurt you in some way?
What?
- 뭐?
- "전화해보지 그래?"
"Why don't you call him?"
정말 고맙구나
준비까지 시켜준다는데
Thank you very much.
Now he's gonna prep her...
남자친구랑 헤어질 수 있게
준비시켜 준다잖아
...as in what you do before
you surgically remove the boyfriend!
미쳤어?
Are you crazy?
내가? 내가 미쳤냐고?
정신나갔냐고?
Am l? Am I out of my mind?
Am I losing my senses?
환상 속의 남자가 내 여자랑
점심을 먹을 거라잖아
This dreamy guy's taking my girlfriend
out for a meal!
이건 오빠랑 상관없는 일이야
This isn't even about you!
레이첼한테 기적같은 일이
일어난 거라구
It's about something wonderful
happening for Rachel.
Even if you're right,
and he wants to sleep with her...
오빠 말대로 그 남자가
꼬신다고 레이첼이 넘어갈까?
...does that mean he gets to?
- 아니...
- 레이첼을 못 믿어?
-No, but
-Don't you trust her?
아니, 믿어
그럼 과감해져
철 좀 들라구!
Then get over yourself!
Grow up!
너 잘났다
You grow up.
맛이 기막힌데요
This tiramisu is excellent.
Did you make it, Mary Angela?
메리 안젤라가
만들었어요?
아니, 내가 만들었어
No, I did.
맛있네요
Well, it's yummy.
메리 안젤라, 맛있어요?
So....
Mary Angela, do you like it?
그럼, 제일 좋아하는 거지
Of course.
It's her favorite.
두 번째 좋아하는 건 뭐예요,
메리 안젤라?
So....
Mary Angela, what's
your second favorite?
내가 만든 건 다 좋아해
More of Grandma's tiramisu.
제발 좀...
Oh, would you just please...
어떻게 만드는지 조리법을
가르쳐줘요, 너무 맛있어요
...give me your recipe, because
this is great! It's topnotch!
절대 안돼
That dies with me.
그렇겠죠
So will l.
Excuse yourself
and go to the bathroom.
잠깐 화장실에 갈래요?
곁눈질 좀 한 걸 갖고...
아무 의미 없어요
I was just squinting.
It doesn't mean anything.
가요
Just do it!
그럼 잠깐 실례...
Will you excuse me, I have to....
이런!
이제 겨우 둘만 남았군요
솔직히 말해요?
Finally! I thought we'd
never be alone.
Can I just tell you something?
파티 끝나고부터 당신 생각을
떨칠 수가 없었어요
I have not stopped thinking about you
since the party.
내가 실수했어요
Look, I may have jumped the gun here.
여자랑 헤어진지 얼마 안돼서
생각없이 사고를 친 거예요
I just got out of a relationship.
And I'm not really in a...
...in a commitment kind of place.
나도 그래요, 메리 안젤라
말대로 입술이 정말 부드럽네요
So? Me neither!
God, Mary Angela was right.
You do have the softest lips.
메리 안젤라 아니에요?
You're not Mary Angela?
난 메리 테레사예요
No! I'm Mary Therese!
This is so bad.
이럴 수가
당신이 메리 안젤라가
아니면 누가 메리 안젤라죠?
If you're not Mary Angela,
then who is?
저요
I am.
이럴 수가
Oh, it's so bad.
조이!
No, Joey! No, Joey!
안돼요, 안돼요, 조이!
무슨 일이야?
What's going on?
찾았다!
이제 우리가 숨을 차례야
You're it!
Now run and hide!
별 거 아냐
It's no big deal.
Chandler was just kissing me...
내가 메리 안젤라인줄 알고
챈들러가 나한테 키스했어
... because he thought
I was Mary Angela.
어떻게 그럴 수가 있어?
얘를 메리 안젤라로 생각했어?
What? How could you
think she was Mary Angela?
누가 메리 안젤라인지
모르겠어
I wasn't sure which one
Mary Angela was.
미안해, 진탕 술에 취했는데
다 비슷하게 생겨서 말야
Look, I'm sorry.
I was really drunk...
...and you guys
all look really similar.
- 한 대 패줘
- 그래, 패줘!
-I say punch him, Joey!
-Yeah, punch him!
다 진정하는 게 좋겠어요
조이는 날 때리지 않아요
We should all calm down...
... because your brother's
not gonna punch me.
Are you?
맞지?
원래는 그런 사람이
아니지만...
That's usually what I'd do.
But I never thought you'd be
on the receiving end.
네가 이럴 줄은 몰랐어
어떻게 이럴 수가 있어?
How could you do this?
날 때리고 싶으면 때려
난 맞아도 싸
If you wanna punch me, go ahead.
I deserve it.
하지만 너나 네 가족에게
상처줄 생각은 아니었어
But I want you to know that I'd never
soberly hurt you or your family.
넌 내 소중한 친구야
다시는 이런 일 없을 거야
You're my best friend.
And I'd never do anything
like this, ever again.
헛소리하지 마
한 대 패주라니까
So what?
-I say punch him!
-Yeah, punch him!
그래, 패줘!
아니
난 챈들러를 때리지 않아
No, I'm not gonna punch Chandler.
- 그럼 내가 때리지
- 아니
-I'll do it.
-No, you won't!
이 친구가 끔찍한 짓을
저질렀지만 난 이 친구를 믿어
He knows he did a terrible thing,
and I believe him. He's sorry.
하지만 사과할 사람이 있어
메리 안젤라한테 사과해
But you got one more apology to make.
You gotta apologize to Mary Angela.
- 그럼, 그래야지
- 좋아
-Absolutely. You got it.
-All right.
- 쿠키, 손 좀 봐줘
- 뭐?
-Cookie, now you can punch him!
-What?
- 안녕
What are you doing here?
여긴 웬일이야?
이 건물에 볼 일이 있어서...
You know, this building's
on my paper route, so....
- 안녕
How did it go?
어떻게 됐어?
나 면접 본 여자가 좀
깐깐하게 굴었는데...
The woman I interviewed with
was pretty tough...
마크 말대로 가을 경향 얘길
했더니 엄청 좋아하는 거 있지?
... but thank God Mark coached me.
Once I talked about the Fall line,
she got all happy.
-I'm so proud of you.
-Me too!
- 자기가 자랑스러워
- 나도 그래!
이상하게 굴어서 미안해
질투가 나서 그랬어
Listen, I'm....
I'm sorry I've been
so crazy and jealous and....
내가 자길 너무 좋아하잖아
It's just,
I like you a lot, so....
알아
I know.
그래?
- 레이첼
- 네
-Hi.
-Hi, Mark.
안녕, 마크
방금 조아나를 만나고 왔는데
맘에 든다고 채용하겠대요
I just talked to Joanna,
and she loves you. You got the job.
- 정말요?
- 그래요
I did?
Oh, my God!
- 세상에
- 축...
Congratulations....
...하해, 축하해
피비, 데이트 어땠어?
So, Phoebe?
How was your date?
알잖아
Oh, well, you know....
그럼, 알지
Yeah, I do know.
You were eavesdropping?
엿들은 거야?
Eavesdropping? Pheebs, the ceiling
tiles were falling down.
엿들었냐고?
천정 타일이 다 떨어지겠더라
Oh, I'm sorry.
미안해
나 그 사람 정말 좋아
그 사람도 날 좋아하고
But I really like this guy
and I think he really likes me.
저 친구 스카이콩콩을
엄청 좋아하나봐
Maybe he's just...
...jumping on a pogo stick
and he really likes it.
Maybe the pogo stick likes it too.
스카이콩콩도 좋은가 본데
더는 못 참아
피비한테 이런 짓을 하다니
All right, that's it.
He cannot do this to Phoebe!
당장 올라가서
혼내줘야겠어
This guy's gonna get
the butt-kicking of a lifetime!
근데... 덩치 크니?
But is he a big guy?
We'll all go. Come on.
다 같이 올라가자
고마워, 얘들아
Thanks, you guys.
Thank you!
Don't worry!
걱정하지 마
God!
I hope they kick his ass!
혼 좀 나야 돼
정말 안됐어
Honey, I'm sorry.
위로가 될지 모르겠지만
너랑 있을 때 더 찐하게 들렸어
If it's any consolation...
...he sounded like
he had more fun with you.